Kaido!
This one's gonna end it, Kaido!
Not now!
Straw Hat?!
When did you get hit?!
That's not what happened.
It's a side effect of that
wrecking ball technique!
He won't be able to use haki
for about ten minutes!
Makes sense. All that power comes at a cost.
Still, if all of those punches actually hurt him,
now's our chance to finish the job!
Don't push your luck!
Luffy! You're dead if you don't get moving!
What's that? Already tapped out?
That was quite the tantrum!
But now, it's lights out for you!
Happy Mother's...
Blaze!
Now hand over Straw Hat!
Countershock!
Luffy! Wake up!
Let's keep up the pressure on Kaido, Killer!
Okay!
Killer! Watch out!
The wind that blows heavenward...
destroys all in its wake...
Dragon Twister!
Killer!
You've got to be kidding!
It's like a natural disaster!
Zoro...! Thanks...
Yeah.
Luffy!
Hold it!
You don't get to eat our captain,
you son of a bitch!
I see!
That strange haki is coming from his sword!
Three-Sword Style:
Black Rope Great Dragon Twister!
He sliced through his scales!
That punk! He cut Kaido!
Oh, you got me good!
I see...
Just as I thought, that sword...
belonged to Oden, didn't it?
You dare to challenge
my own Dragon Twister...
I'll put you in your place!
Hey! Luffy!
Oh, Zoro...?
Something big is coming!
Dragon Twister...
Demolition Gust!
What a pain...
First, our supplier dies,
then the banquet that we're
invited to turns into a battlefield.
Apparently, this battle is to avenge a man
who was killed in Wano twenty years ago.
Yeah...
But when Doflamingo fell from power,
this clash between Kaido
and the Worst Generation became inevitable.
It was fate...
that brought the samurai
and the pirates together.
With the world order
hanging on a knife's edge...
Imagine if both of those
Emperors were to somehow fall...
There's no telling what would
happen to the world.
But we needn't worry about that.
The enemy invaders...
number 5,400.
But 400 have fallen.
On the other hand,
we Beast Pirates...
number 30,000.
But 3,000 of them have already fallen.
The samurai have done well.
The difference in numbers is so vast
that a direct attack would never reach the leader.
Their infiltration plan
has worked out brilliantly.
But in this battle, simply taking
the leader's head won't cut it.
This is an all-out war.
There's no refuge on the island.
If Kaido's top officers are left unchecked...
each will easily eliminate
100 soldiers at a time.
If this new generation
can't stop the top officers...
...this game of go will end
with all black pieces on the board.
The outcome of this battle
has already been decided.
Crush one another as much as you want...
my dear pirates.
Why does he look like that?
Is that his hybrid form?
Hey, Linlin!
Isn't this fun?
You took the words right out of my mouth!
Kaido!
Listen up, fellas!
To break this deadlock,
His Awesomeness, Queen,
has entrusted me with a secret weapon.
Looking hot as ever, Madam Speed!
So, where is this "secret weapon"?
Right here.
It'll dramatically boost your body's healing,
and improve muscle strength...
significantly!
What?!
Are you for real?!
That said...
it looks really delicious...
Give me that dumpling immediately!
Looks like you got pretty roughed up, Briscola.
Shut up!
If I don't get my revenge against
those annoying, shitty Straw Hats,
I'll never be satisfied!
I'll let you have one, then.
Just one bite will flip your world upside down.
Here.
How is it, Briscola?
Feels like it's working...
Or maybe not...
No way.
Huh?
You fool...
You're not trying to say that
Queen's homemade dumpling...
is a failure, are you?
Gulp!
Boing!
Boing! Boing! Boing!
Wee!
It's amazing!
I feel pure power coursing through my veins!
That's awesome!
I want one too, Boss Briscola!
Madam Speed! Might I have a dumpling too?
I want one too!
– Two for us!
Of course!
I've got enough here for every last Gifter!
– Yay!
– Delicious!
Once you finish eating, get ready to fight!
There's no time to waste!
The Straw Hats won't wait for us!
Horsella!
I wanna go to Onigashima, too!
No one let me go with them...
So...
Leave it to me, Master!
Millet Dumpling!
Every one of these brings us another ally!
Millet Dumpling...
Millet Dumpling!
Millet Dump–
Master, I think you'd better stop now...
I'm okay...
There's no way I can
bring Kaido down all by myself...
So...
I have to do whatever I can to help!
I want a Wano without Orochi and Kaido,
with Momo as the shogun!
That's the future I want to see!
And I'm tired of being hungry all the time...
I wanna eat...
I understand.
Let's fight!
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's have something to eat first, and then
we'll lie in wait for our chance to strike!
– Okay!
– All right!
Ready...
Start!
Eat this!
Huh?! It's delicious!
– Delicious!
Eat this!
Delicious!
Eat up, Gifters!
Look! It's the vice warden
from Udon, Daifugo!
Take him down!
You put us through hell!
Sorry about that, guys!
Let's just put it aside for a bit!
What?!
– Oh, Daifugo, sir! Thank you for your hard work!
No time for pleasantries!
Eat this!
Eat this! Serve the master!
General Left!
We're not done yet!
Sasaki, sir!
This is it!
General–
Hold him down!
Hey, come on!
Outta the way, you bums!
You may be strong, but even you
can't shake off this many of us!
Didn't you know? We Gifters
have been given special abilities!
We're no ordinary soldiers!
These are some real tough customers...
– Franky!
That must be...
Usopp! Nami! And Otama!
Wha... why?!
Wait, this is no time for questions!
Good timing! Help me get these guys off of–
– Help!
They're being chased by
everyone and their mother!
For crying out loud!
Things just went from bad to worse!
Gifters! Push ahead and block the way!
When it comes to numbers,
we have the advantage!
They can't win unless
the tide turns all over the island!
What am I supposed to do?!
I...
I'm here to turn that tide!
Everyone, please!
Franosuke needs you!
Help him!
– Got it, Master!
What?!
Alright!
Whew! That was close!
Great work, guys!
What the hell are you dolts thinking?!
Sasaki!
Page One! Ulti!
They've switched sides! Trample them all!
Switched sides?!
What could they possibly gain
by siding with the samurai?
It's probably one of their abilities!
Isn't that right?!
You really are asking for
a crushed skull this time!
Not again!
Lightning alert!
This one's a real
heart-stopper, so look alive!
Thunder Lance...
Tempo!
Big Sis!
Damn! That hurts!
She's done it now! That rotten bitch!
I knew that wouldn't be enough...
I need more powerful lightning!
She used some weird trick!
Guys! Take them down!
They'll only get in our way if we leave them be!
– Aye, aye, Sasaki!
Not on my watch!
Lethal...
Millet Dumpling Star!
What was that?
Everybody!
Follow me!
– Aye, aye, Master!
Huh?!
What?! Hey! What's going on?!
Wait, Armored Division!
Whoa there.
You oughta stay focused.
Did you forget...
who you're fighting?
Franken-Sword...
V-for-Victory Flash!
Damn...
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Be a good boy.
Black Leg Sanji.
My goodness...
Such a cute boy, acting out like this.
So much power, but what a shame...
You beat the hell out of the men,
but you can't even lay a finger on the women.
It seems your chances of victory
have dropped to zero.
Your life is in the palm of my hand.
Now then, it's time for you to call out...
for Nico Robin!
This is Caiman Lady.
If you speak loudly to this woman...
your voice will be heard all over the castle.
After that, I'll set you free.
Those were Kaido's orders.
What are you gonna do to Robin?
Let's see...
We'll gang up on her, capture her...
and maim her limbs until she's paralyzed.
Only once we're "finished" with her,
which could take years and years,
will we finally kill her.
So don't you worry.
Damn you...
Don't underestimate Nico Robin!
Detected! Detected!
Red Scabbard samurai, detected!
It seems they've escaped the rooftop battle!
Bloodied and beaten!
But still breathing, it seems!
Location... behind the castle tower!
The second floor of the treasury
at the second bailey!
They must've escaped from Kaido.
I've got my hands full over here.
Can someone else handle it?
Go to the treasury right away
and kill all the samurai!
Did you get all of that, Madame Black Maria?
Yes, King...
I'll go.
This floor is connected to
the second floor of the treasury.
Want me to finish the Red Scabbards off?
Yeah, thanks!
Kin'emon... They all lost?!
Wait! Don't go!
But be careful! There are ten people...
in that room!
It's hard to make out in the darkness,
but someone is trying to help the samurai!
Hurry up and kill them!
Someone's...
in there!